Farnaz Towhidi . Jarvis Consulting

Full stack developer with years of experience in designing and developing user interface, testing, debugging, implementing components in amazing companies like IBM, Canadian Institute of Cyber Security and Biossentials. I always feel passionate about increasing the limits to academic knowledge thus my PHD and increasing the knowledge in General Assembly of Toronto.

Skills

Proficient: Html/CSS, JavaScript, RDBMS/SQL, Agile/Scrum, Sql

Competent: OOP, MVC Pattern, Oath Authentication, fermentum, Donec

Familiar: Docker, fermentum, fermentum, Selenium, Jira

Jarvis Projects

Project source code: https://github.com/Jarvis-Consulting-Group/jarvis_data_eng-FarnazTowhidi

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

- Twitter App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- JDBC App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- Grep App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.

Springboot App [GitHub]: Not Started

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: Not Started

Hadoop [GitHub]: Not StartedSpark [GitHub]: Not Started

Cloud/DevOps [GitHub]: Not Started

Highlighted Projects

Web app for resturant [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Machine Learning: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Professional Experiences

Software Developer, Jarvis (2023-present): Donec mattis sed justo et sagittis. Vestibulum lacinia nulla ipsum. Curabitur imperdiet nibh vitae leo lacinia laoreet. Nullam accumsan, lectus ut maximus ultricies, augue justo egestas mi, vel bibendum felis.

Quality Assurance, IBM (Fredericton) (2020-2020): Part of security intelligence team of 10 working on QRadar that ensured the testing algorithms and probability threat analysis was maintained at peak efficiency. Created and edited automated test cases, manual, automation and regression testing. Maintained the Knowledge on QRadar log and network activity and reports.

Education

XYZ university (2012-2016), Bachelor of Applied Sciences, Electrical and Computer Engineering - Scholarship - Dean's List (2015, 2016): Ut enim ad minim veniam - GPA: 3.8/4.0

XYZ university (2016-2018), Master of Engineering, Electrical and Computer Engineering

Miscellaneous

- Udacity Machine Learning (2019)
- Winner
- Basketball player
- Competitive gaming
- Volunteer, ABC Food bank: Ut enim ad minim veniam